<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<add>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000332038500042</field>
        <field name="title">Spin caloritronics in graphene with Mn</field>
        <field name="Author">Alberto Torres</field>
        <field name="Author">Matheus P. Lima</field>
        <field name="Author">A. Fazzio</field>
        <field name="Author">Antonio J. R. da Silva</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">AMER INST PHYSICS | APPLIED PHYSICS LETTERS | 104</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">We show that graphene with Mn adatoms trapped at single vacancies
            features spin-dependent Seebeck effect, thus enabling the use of this
            material for spin caloritronics. A gate potential can be used to tune
            its thermoelectric properties in a way it presents either a total spin
            polarized current, flowing in one given direction, or currents for both
            spins flowing in opposite directions without net charge transport.
            Moreover, we show that the thermal magnetoresistance can be tuned
            between -100\% and +100\% by varying a gate potential. (C) 2014 AIP
            Publishing LLC.
        </field>
        <field name="address">USA</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1063/1.4866184</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0003-6951</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1077-3118</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">TRANSPORT</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CONDUCTANCE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">FORMULA</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Physics</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Physics, Applied</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">31</field>
        <field name="times-cited">12</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Appl. Phys. Lett.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331349600002</field>
        <field name="title">Application of loop-mediated isothermal amplification assays for direct
            identification of pure cultures of Aspergillus flavus, A. nomius, and A.
            caelatus and for their rapid detection in shelled Brazil nuts
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Jie Luo</field>
        <field name="Author">Marta H. Taniwaki</field>
        <field name="Author">Beatriz T. Iamanaka</field>
        <field name="Author">F. Rudi Vogel</field>
        <field name="Author">Ludwig Niessen</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE BV | INTERNATIONAL JOURNAL OF FOOD MICROBIOLOGY | 172
        </field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Brazil nuts have a high nutritional content and are a very important
            trade commodity for some Latin American countries. Aflatoxins are
            carcinogenic fungal secondary metabolites. In Brazil nuts they are
            produced predominantly by Aspergillus (A.) nomius and A. flavus. In the
            present study we applied and evaluated two sets of primers previously
            published for the specific detection of the two species using
            loop-mediated isothermal amplification (LAMP) technology. Moreover, a
            primer set specific for A. caelatus as a frequently occurring
            non-aflatoxigenic member of Aspergillus section Flavi in Brazil nuts was
            newly developed. LAMP assays were combined with a simplified DNA release
            method and used for rapid identification of pure cultures and rapid
            detection of A. nomius and A. flavus from samples of shelled Brazil
            nuts. An analysis of pure cultures of 68 isolates representing the major
            Aspergillus species occurring on Brazil nuts showed that the three LAMP
            assays had individual accuracies of 61.5\%, 84.4\%, and 93.3\% for A.
            flavus, A. nomius, and A. caelatus, respectively when morphological
            identification was used as a reference. The detection limits for conidia
            added directly to the individual LAMP reactions were found to be 10(5)
            conidia per reaction with the primer set ID9 for A. nomius and 10(4)
            conidia per reaction with the primer set ID58 for A. flavus. Sensitivity
            was increased to 10(1) and 10(2) conidia per reaction for A. nom. ius
            and A. flavus, respectively, when sample preparation included a spore
            disruption step. The results of LAMP assays obtained during the analysis
            of 32 Brazil nut samples from different regions of Brazil and from
            different steps in the production process of the commodity were compared
            with results obtained from mycological analysis and aflatoxin analysis
            of corresponding samples. Compared with mycological analysis of the
            samples, the Negative Predictive Values of LAMP assays were 42.1\% and
            12.5\% while the Positive Predictive Values were 61.5\% and 66.7\% for
            A. nomius and A. flavus, respectively. When LAMP results were compared
            with the presence of aflatoxins in corresponding samples, the Negative
            Predictive Values were 22.2\% and 44.4\% and the Positive Predictive
            Values were 52.2\% and 78.3\% for aflatoxins produced by A. nomius and
            A. flavus, respectively. The LAMP assays described in this study have
            been demonstrated to be a specific, sensitive and easy to use tool for
            the survey of Brazil nuts for contaminations with potential
            aflatoxin-producing A. nomius and A. flavus in low tech environments
            where resources may be limited. (C) 2013 Elsevier B.V. All rights
            reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">NETHERLANDS</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.ijfoodmicro.2013.12.001</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0168-1605</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1879-3460</field>
        <field name="keyword">Loop-mediated isothermal amplification</field>
        <field name="keyword">A. nomius</field>
        <field name="keyword">A. flavus</field>
        <field name="keyword">A.</field>
        <field name="keyword">caelatus</field>
        <field name="keyword">Brazil nut</field>
        <field name="keyword">Rapid detection</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SECTION FLAVI</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">AFLATOXIGENIC MOLDS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">VISUAL DETECTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">LAMP</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DNA</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">FOOD</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">FUNGI</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PCR</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SELENIUM</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GROWTH</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Food Science \&amp; Technology; Microbiology</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Food Science \&amp; Technology; Microbiology</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">43</field>
        <field name="times-cited">9</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Int. J. Food Microbiol.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000334012400007</field>
        <field name="title">Antioxidant and intestinal anti-inflammatory effects of plant-derived
            coumarin derivatives
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Aline Witaicenis</field>
        <field name="Author">Leonardo Noboru Seito</field>
        <field name="Author">Silveira Alexandre da Chagas</field>
        <field name="Author">Luiz Domingues de Almeida Junior</field>
        <field name="Author">Ana Carolina Luchini</field>
        <field name="Author">Patricia Rodrigues-Orsi</field>
        <field name="Author">Silvia Helena Cestari</field>
        <field name="Author">Luiz Claudio Di Stasi</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER GMBH, URBAN \&amp; FISCHER VERLAG | PHYTOMEDICINE | 21</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Background: Coumarins, also known as benzopyrones, are plant-derived
            products with several pharmacological properties, including antioxidant
            and anti-inflammatory activities. Based on the wide distribution of
            coumarin derivatives in plant-based foods and beverages in the human
            diet, our objective was to evaluate both the antioxidant and intestinal
            anti-inflammatory activities of six coumarin derivatives of plant origin
            (scopoletin, scoparone, fraxetin, 4-methyl-umbeliferone, esculin and
            daphnetin) to verify if potential intestinal anti-inflammatory activity
            was related to antioxidant properties.
            Methods: Intestinal inflammation was induced by intracolonic
            instillation of TNBS in rats. The animals were treated with coumarins by
            oral route. The animals were killed 48 h after colitis induction. The
            colonic segments were obtained after laparotomy and macroscopic and
            biochemical parameters (determination of glutathione level and
            myeloperoxidase and alkaline phosphatase activities) were evaluated. The
            antioxidant properties of these coumarins were examined by lipid
            peroxidation and DPPH assays.
            Results: Treatment with esculin, scoparone and daphnetin produced the
            best protective effects. All coumarin derivatives showed antioxidant
            activity in the DPPH assay, while daphnetin and fraxetin also showed
            antioxidant activity by inhibiting lipid peroxidation. Coumarins, except
            4-methyl-umbeliferone, also showed antioxidant activity through the
            counteraction of glutathione levels or through the inhibition of
            myeloperoxidase activity.
            Discussion: The intestinal anti-inflammatory activity of coumarin
            derivatives were related to their antioxidant properties, suggesting
            that consumption of coumarins and/or foods rich in coumarin derivatives,
            particularly daphnetin, esculin and scoparone, could prevent intestinal
            inflammatory disease. (C) 2013 Elsevier GmbH. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">GERMANY</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.phymed.2013.09.001</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0944-7113</field>
        <field name="keyword">Coumarin derivatives</field>
        <field name="keyword">Antioxidant</field>
        <field name="keyword">Inflammatory bowel disease</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">INFLAMMATORY-BOWEL-DISEASE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">TRINITROBENZENESULFONIC ACID MODEL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">OXIDATIVE STRESS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">RAT COLITIS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">4-METHYLESCULETIN</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SULFASALAZINE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GLUTATHIONE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">METABOLISM</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">INDUCTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ESCULETIN</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Plant Sciences; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine
        </field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Plant Sciences; Chemistry, Medicinal; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy
        </field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">38</field>
        <field name="times-cited">79</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Phytomedicine</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000334012400019</field>
        <field name="title">Nitensidine A, a guanidine alkaloid from Pterogyne nitens, is a novel
            substrate for human ABC transporter ABCB1
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Yasuhiro Tajima</field>
        <field name="Author">Hiroshi Nakagawa</field>
        <field name="Author">Ai Tamura</field>
        <field name="Author">Onat Kadioglu</field>
        <field name="Author">Kazuhiro Satake</field>
        <field name="Author">Yuji Mitani</field>
        <field name="Author">Hayato Murase</field>
        <field name="Author">Luis Octavio Regasini</field>
        <field name="Author">Vanderlan da Silva Bolzani</field>
        <field name="Author">Toshihisa Ishikawa</field>
        <field name="Author">Gert Fricker</field>
        <field name="Author">Thomas Efferth</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER GMBH, URBAN \&amp; FISCHER VERLAG | PHYTOMEDICINE | 21</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">The Pterogyne nitens (Fabaceae) tree, native to South America, has been
            found to produce guanidine alkaloids as well as bioactive flavonols such
            as kaempferol, quercetin, and rutin. In the present study, we examined
            the possibility of interaction between human ATP-binding cassette (ABC)
            transporter ABCB1 and four guanidine alkaloids isolated from P. nitens
            (i.e., galegine, nitensidine A, pterogynidine, and pterogynine) using
            human T cell lymphoblast-like leukemia cell line CCRF-CEM and its
            multi-drug resistant (MDR) counterpart CEM/ADR5000. In XTT assays,
            CEM/ADR5000 cells were resistant to the four guanidine alkaloids
            compared to CCRF-CEM cells, although the four guanidine alkaloids
            exhibited some level of cytotoxicity against both CCRF-CEM and
            CEM/ADR5000 cells. In ATPase assays, three of the four guanidine
            alkaloids were found to stimulate the ATPase activity of ABCB1. Notably,
            nitensidine A was clearly found to stimulate the ATPase activity of
            ABCB1 as strongly as the control drug, verapamil. Furthermore, the
            cytotoxic effect of nitensidine A on CEM/ADR5000 cells was
            synergistically enhanced by verapamil. Nitensidine A inhibited the
            extrusion of calcein by ABCB1. In the present study, the possibility of
            interaction between ABCB1 and two synthetic nitensidine A analogs
            (nitensidine AT and AU) were examined to gain insight into the mechanism
            by which nitensidine A stimulates the ATPase activity of ABCB1. The
            ABCB1-dependent ATPase activity stimulated by nitensidine A was greatly
            reduced by substituting sulfur (S) or oxygen (0) for the imino nitrogen
            atom (N) in nitensidine A. Molecular docking studies on human ABCB1
            showed that, guanidine alkaloids from P. nitens dock to the same binding
            pocket as verapamil. Nitensidine A and its analogs exhibit similar
            binding energies to verapamil. Taken together, this research clearly
            indicates that nitensidine A is a novel substrate for ABCB1. The present
            results also suggest that the number, binding site, and polymerization
            degree of the isoprenyl moiety in the guanidine alkaloids and the imino
            nitrogen atom cooperatively contribute to their stimulation of ABCB1's
            ATPase activity. (C) 2013 Elsevier GmbH. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">GERMANY</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.phymed.2013.08.024</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0944-7113</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1618-095X</field>
        <field name="keyword">ATP-binding cassette (ABC) transporter</field>
        <field name="keyword">ABCB1</field>
        <field name="keyword">P-glycoprotein</field>
        <field name="keyword">Pterogyne</field>
        <field name="keyword">nitens</field>
        <field name="keyword">Guanidine alkaloid</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MODULATE MULTIDRUG RESISTANCE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">P-GLYCOPROTEIN GENE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PHARMACOPHORE MODEL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CELLS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">INHIBITION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">HOMOLOGY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">REVERSAL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ANALOGS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SERIES</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DRUGS</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Plant Sciences; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine
        </field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Plant Sciences; Chemistry, Medicinal; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy
        </field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">36</field>
        <field name="times-cited">14</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Phytomedicine</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000334012400023</field>
        <field name="title">The oral administration of trans-caryophyllene attenuates acute and
            chronic pain in mice
        </field>
        <field name="Author">L. I. G. Paula-Freire</field>
        <field name="Author">M. L. Andersen</field>
        <field name="Author">V. S. Gama</field>
        <field name="Author">G. R. Molska</field>
        <field name="Author">E. L. A. Carlini</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER GMBH, URBAN \&amp; FISCHER VERLAG | PHYTOMEDICINE | 21</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Trans-caryophyllene is a sesquiterpene present in many medicinal plants'
            essential oils, such as Ocimum gratissimum and Cannabis sativa. In this
            study, we evaluated the antinociceptive activity of transcaryophyllene
            in murine models of acute and chronic pain and the involvement of
            trans-caryophyllene in the opioid and endocannabinoid systems. Acute
            pain was determined using the hot plate test (thermal nociception) and
            the formalin test (inflammatory pain). The chronic constriction injury
            (CCI) of the sciatic nerve induced hypernociception was measured by the
            hot plate and von Frey tests. To elucidate the mechanism of action, mice
            were pre-treated with naloxone or AM630 30 min before the
            trans-caryophyllene treatment. Afterwards, thermal nociception was
            evaluated. The levels of IL-1 beta were measured in CCI-mice by ELISA.
            Trans-caryophyllene administration significantly minimized the pain in
            both the acute and chronic pain models. The antinociceptive effect
            observed during the hot plate test was reversed by naloxone and AM630,
            indicating the participation of both the opioid and endocannabinoid
            system. Trans-caryophyllene treatment also decreased the IL-1 beta
            levels. These results demonstrate that transcaryophyllene reduced both
            acute and chronic pain in mice, which may be mediated through the opioid
            and endocannabinoid systems. (C) 2013 Elsevier GmbH. All rights
            reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">GERMANY</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.phymed.2013.08.006</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0944-7113</field>
        <field name="keyword">Medicinal plants</field>
        <field name="keyword">Trans-caryophyllene</field>
        <field name="keyword">Opioid system</field>
        <field name="keyword">Endocannabinoid</field>
        <field name="keyword">system</field>
        <field name="keyword">Interleukin 1 beta</field>
        <field name="keyword">Pain</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CANNABINOID CB2 RECEPTORS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">NEUROPATHIC PAIN</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ESSENTIAL OIL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">BETA-CARYOPHYLLENE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CORDIA-VERBENACEA</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CHEMICAL-COMPOSITION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">RAT</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ANTINOCICEPTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MODEL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">INTERLEUKIN-1-BETA</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Plant Sciences; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine
        </field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Plant Sciences; Chemistry, Medicinal; Integrative \&amp; Complementary
            Medicine; Pharmacology \&amp; Pharmacy
        </field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">46</field>
        <field name="times-cited">27</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Phytomedicine</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000332811800003</field>
        <field name="title">Valorization of sugarcane bagasse ash: Producing glass-ceramic materials</field>
        <field name="Author">S. R. Teixeira</field>
        <field name="Author">R. S. Magalhaes</field>
        <field name="Author">A. Arenales</field>
        <field name="Author">A. E. Souza</field>
        <field name="Author">M. Romero</field>
        <field name="Author">J. M. Rincon</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ACADEMIC PRESS LTD- ELSEVIER SCIENCE LTD | JOURNAL OF ENVIRONMENTAL
            MANAGEMENT | 134
        </field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Some aluminosilicates, for example mullite and wollastonite, are very
            important in the ceramic and construction industries. The most
            significant glass-ceramic for building applications has wollastonite as
            the main crystal phase. In this work we report on the use of sugarcane
            bagasse ash (SCBA) to produce glass-ceramics with silicates as the major
            crystalline phases. The glasses (frits) were prepared by mixing ash,
            limestone (calcium and magnesium carbonates) and potassium carbonate as
            the fluxing agent. X-ray fluorescence was used to determine the chemical
            composition of the glasses and their crystallization was assessed by
            using thermal analysis (DTA/DSC/TGA) and X-ray diffraction. The results
            showed that glass-ceramic material can be produced with wollastonite as
            the major phase, at a temperature lower than 900 degrees C. (C) 2014
            Elsevier Ltd. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">ENGLAND</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.jenvman.2013.12.029</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0301-4797</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1095-8630</field>
        <field name="keyword">Wollastonite</field>
        <field name="keyword">Sugarcane</field>
        <field name="keyword">Ash</field>
        <field name="keyword">Limestone</field>
        <field name="keyword">Glass-ceramic</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">FLY-ASH</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CRYSTALLIZATION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">REPLACEMENT</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">RESIDUE</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Environmental Sciences \&amp; Ecology</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Environmental Sciences</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">23</field>
        <field name="times-cited">15</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">J. Environ. Manage.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000333139200007</field>
        <field name="title">Kefir administration reduced progression of renal injury in STZ-diabetic
            rats by lowering oxidative stress
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Giovana R. Punaro</field>
        <field name="Author">Fabiane R. Maciel</field>
        <field name="Author">Adelson M. Rodrigues</field>
        <field name="Author">Marcelo M. Rogero</field>
        <field name="Author">Cristina S. B. Bogsan</field>
        <field name="Author">Marice N. Oliveira</field>
        <field name="Author">Silvia S. M. Ihara</field>
        <field name="Author">Sergio R. R. Araujo</field>
        <field name="Author">C. Talita R. Sanches</field>
        <field name="Author">Lucia C. Andrade</field>
        <field name="Author">Elisa M. S. Higa</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ACADEMIC PRESS INC ELSEVIER SCIENCE | NITRIC OXIDE-BIOLOGY AND CHEMISTRY
            | 37
        </field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">This study aimed at assessing the effects of Kefir, a probiotic
            fermented milk, on oxidative stress in diabetic animals. The induction
            of diabetes was achieved in adult male Wistar rats using streptozotocin
            (STZ). The animals were distributed into four groups as follows: control
            (CTL); control Kefir (CTLK); diabetic (DM) and diabetic Kefir (DMK).
            Starting on the 5th day of diabetes, Kefir was administered by daily
            gavage at a dose of 1.8 mL/day for 8 weeks. Before and after Kefir
            treatment, the rats were placed in individual metabolic cages to obtain
            blood and urine samples to evaluate urea, creatinine, proteinuria,
            nitric oxide (NO), thiobarbituric acid reactive substances (TBARS) and
            C-reactive protein (CRP). After sacrificing the animals, the renal
            cortex was removed for histology, oxidative stress and NOS evaluation.
            When compared to CTL rats, DM rats showed increased levels of glycemia,
            plasmatic urea, proteinuria, renal NO, superoxide anion, TBARS, and
            plasmatic CRP; also demonstrated a reduction in urinary urea,
            creatinine, and NO. However, DMK rats showed a significant improvement
            in most of these parameters. Despite the lack of differences observed in
            the expression of endothelial NO synthase (eNOS), the expression of
            inducible NO synthase (iNOS) was significantly lower in the DMK group
            when compared to DM rats, as assessed by Western blot analysis.
            Moreover, the DMK group presented a significant reduction of glycogen
            accumulation within the renal tubules when compared to the DM group.
            These results indicate that Kefir treatment may contribute to better
            control of glycemia and oxidative stress, which is associated with the
            amelioration of renal function, suggesting its use as a
            non-pharmacological adjuvant to delay the progression of diabetic
            complications. (C) 2014 Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">USA</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.niox.2013.12.012</field>
        <field name="ISSN">1089-8603</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1089-8611</field>
        <field name="keyword">Kefir</field>
        <field name="keyword">Oxidative stress</field>
        <field name="keyword">Nitric oxide</field>
        <field name="keyword">Diabetes and renal function</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">C-REACTIVE PROTEIN</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">NITRIC-OXIDE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MELLITUS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">KIDNEY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DIET</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PERMEABILITY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">NEPHROPATHY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DYSFUNCTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DISEASE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MODELS</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Biochemistry \&amp; Molecular Biology; Cell Biology</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Biochemistry \&amp; Molecular Biology; Cell Biology</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">41</field>
        <field name="times-cited">13</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Nitric Oxide-Biol. Chem.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331779600107</field>
        <field name="title">Impregnation of cinnamaldehyde into cassava starch biocomposite films
            using supercritical fluid technology for the development of food active
            packaging
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Ana Cristina de Souza</field>
        <field name="Author">Ana M. A. Dias</field>
        <field name="Author">Herminio C. Sousa</field>
        <field name="Author">Carmen C. Tadini</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCI LTD | CARBOHYDRATE POLYMERS | 102</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">In this work, supercritical solvent impregnation (SSI) has been tested
            for the incorporation of natural compounds into biocomposite materials
            for food packaging. Cinnamaldehyde, with proved antimicrobial activity
            against fungi commonly found in bread products, was successfully
            impregnated on biocomposite cassava starch based materials using
            supercritical carbon dioxide as solvent. Different process experimental
            conditions were tested (pressure, impregnation time and depressurization
            rate) at a fixed temperature (35 C) in order to study their influence on
            the amount of impregnated cinnamaldehyde as well as on the morphology of
            the films. Results showed that all conditions permitted to impregnate
            antimicrobial active amounts superior to those previously obtained using
            conventional incorporation methods. Moreover, a significant decrease of
            the equilibrium water vapor sorption capacity and water vapor
            permeability of the films was observed after SSI processing which is a
            clear advantage of the process, considering the envisaged applications.
            (C) 2013 Elsevier Ltd. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">ENGLAND</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.carbpol.2013.10.082</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0144-8617</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1879-1344</field>
        <field name="keyword">Cassava starch</field>
        <field name="keyword">Antimicrobial agent</field>
        <field name="keyword">Supercritical solvent impregnation</field>
        <field name="keyword">Food packaging</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ESCHERICHIA-COLI O157-H7</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PLANT ESSENTIAL OILS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SOLVENT IMPREGNATION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">EDIBLE FILMS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">BARRIER PROPERTIES</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">WATER SORPTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GLYCEROL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CLAY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GROWTH</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SOLUBILITY</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Chemistry; Polymer Science</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Chemistry, Applied; Chemistry, Organic; Polymer Science</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">39</field>
        <field name="times-cited">20</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Carbohydr. Polym.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331989900003</field>
        <field name="title">Copper-tin electrodeposition from an acid solution containing EDTA added</field>
        <field name="Author">E. P. Barbano</field>
        <field name="Author">G. M. de Oliveira</field>
        <field name="Author">M. F. de Carvalho</field>
        <field name="Author">I. A. Carlos</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE SA | SURFACE \&amp; COATINGS TECHNOLOGY | 240</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">An acid Cu-Sn deposition bath was developed, containing EDTA (disodium
            ethylenediaminetetraacetate) to sequester the copper(II) and tin(II)
            ions, forming stable complexes in solution at pH 3.4. Voltammetric
            studies showed that the onset of Cu-Sn codeposition started with
            reduction of { [ } CuEDTA](2-) and { [ } Sn(H2O)(6)](2+) at potential more
            negative than -0.90 V (first region of deposition). The reduction of
            { [ } SnEDTA](2-) complexes occurs at potential more negative than -1.20 V
            (second region of deposition), leading to Cu-Sn alloys with a higher tin
            content. The hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) occurs in all range of
            potential parallel to the Cu-Sn deposition. No nucleation loop was
            observed in the voltammetric curves for Cu-Sn deposition due to HER.
            Cu-Sn voltammetric deposition at various sweep rates indicated that the
            deposition process may be controlled by mass transport and charge
            transfer in both regions. The Sn content in the potentiostatic Cu-Sn
            (Ed) change, from similar to 27.0 wt.\% to similar to 60.0 wt.\%, for a
            constant composition of deposition bath. Cu-Sn deposit containing 43.6
            wt.\% Sn was obtained from the acid EDTA bath investigated herein. The
            color of the deposits was reddish (similar to 27.0 wt.\% Sn) and grayish
            (similar to 32.0 wt.\% -similar to 60.0 wt.\% Sn).
            Scanning electron microscopy images showed that the deposits produced at
            -1.03 V and -1.30 V, for both deposition charge densities (q(d)), 2.55 C
            cm(-2) and 8.47 C cm(-2), were composed of cauliflower-like particles,
            which increased with qd, and that the deposits obtained at -1.30 V were
            more compact than those formed at -1.03 V, for both qd, being this, the
            main difference between these two types of deposits.
            X-ray patterns of the deposits formed at E-d = -1.03 V, with either
            q(d), using non-grazing incidence, indicated the presence of hcp-CuSn
            and Cu3Sn phases. However, for E-d = -1.30 V were identified the Cu6Sn5
            and Cu10Sn3 phases for q(d) = 2.55 C cm(-2) and only Cu6Sn5 phase for
            q(d) = 8.47 C cm(-2). (C) 2013 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">SWITZERLAND</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.surfcoat.2013.12.005</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0257-8972</field>
        <field name="keyword">Copper-tin</field>
        <field name="keyword">Electrodeposition</field>
        <field name="keyword">EDTA acid bath</field>
        <field name="keyword">Voltammetry</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CU-SN ALLOYS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ALKALINE BATH</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MORPHOLOGICAL CHARACTERIZATION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PLATING</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">BATH</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ZINC ELECTRODEPOSITION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SULFATE-SOLUTIONS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DEPOSITION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">COATINGS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SORBITOL</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">FILMS</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Materials Science; Physics</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Materials Science, Coatings \&amp; Films; Physics, Applied</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">49</field>
        <field name="times-cited">8</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Surf. Coat. Technol.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331851100007</field>
        <field name="title">Forest biomass recovery after conventional and reduced-impact logging in
            Amazonian Brazil
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Thales A. P. West</field>
        <field name="Author">Edson Vidal</field>
        <field name="Author">Francis E. Putz</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE BV | FOREST ECOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT | 314</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Growing concerns about unnecessarily destructive selective logging of
            tropical forests and its impacts on greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions
            motivated this study on post-logging biomass dynamics over a 16-year
            period in a control plot and in plots subjected to conventional logging
            (CL) or reduced-impact logging (RIL) in Paragominas, Para State, Brazil.
            All trees &gt;25 cm were monitored in 25.4 ha plots of each treatment, each
            with a subplot of 5.25 ha for trees &gt;10 cm dbh. The commercial timber
            volumes in felled trees were 38.9 and 37.4 m(3) ha(-1) in the RIL and CL
            plots, respectively, but the extracted volumes were 38.6 and 29.7 m(3)
            ha(-1), respectively. Immediately after logging, plots subjected to RIL
            and CL lost 17\% and 26\% of their above-ground biomass, respectively.
            Over the 16 years after logging, the average annual increments in
            above-ground biomass (recruitment plus residual tree growth minus
            mortality) were 2.8 Mg ha(-1) year(-1) in the RIL plot but only 0.5 Mg
            ha(-1) year in the CL plot. By 16 years post-logging, the RIL plot
            recovered 100\% of its original above-ground biomass while the CL plot
            recovered only 77\%; over the same period, biomass in the control plot
            maintained 96\% of its initial stock. These findings reinforce the claim
            that conversion from CL to RIL would represent an efficient forest-based
            strategy to mitigate climate change under the REDD+ and would be an
            important step towards sustainable forest management. (C) 2013 Elsevier
            B.V. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">NETHERLANDS</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.foreco.2013.11.022</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0378-1127</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1872-7042</field>
        <field name="keyword">Forest management</field>
        <field name="keyword">Biomass</field>
        <field name="keyword">Forest structure</field>
        <field name="keyword">Climate change mitigation</field>
        <field name="keyword">REDD</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ABOVEGROUND LIVE BIOMASS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">TROPICAL FORESTS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">TIMBER PRODUCTION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">EASTERN</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">AMAZONIA</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">CARBON STORAGE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MANAGEMENT</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GROWTH</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Forestry</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Forestry</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">32</field>
        <field name="times-cited">27</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">For. Ecol. Manage.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331686300005</field>
        <field name="title">Cellular bioenergetics changes in magnocellular neurons may affect
            copeptin expression in the late phase of sepsis
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Gabriela R. Oliveira-Pelegrin</field>
        <field name="Author">Paulo J. Basso</field>
        <field name="Author">A. Maria Jose Rocha</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE BV | JOURNAL OF NEUROIMMUNOLOGY | 267</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">We investigated whether inflammatory mediators during cecal ligation and
            puncture (CLP)-induced sepsis may diminish copeptin expression in
            magnocellular neurons, thus affecting arginine-vasopressin (AVP)
            synthesis. The transcript abundance of IL-1 beta, iNOS and HIF-1 alpha
            was continuously elevated. IL-1 beta, iNOS and cytochrome c protein
            levels progressively increased until 24 h. Immunostaining for these
            proteins was higher at 6 and 24 h, as also seen in the annexin-V assay,
            while copeptin was continuously decreased. This suggests that increased
            IL-1 beta and NO levels may cause significant bioenergetics changes in
            magnocellular neurons, affecting copeptin expression and compromising
            AVP synthesis and secretion in the late phase of sepsis. (C) 2013
            Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">NETHERLANDS</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.jneuroim.2013.12.006</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0165-5728</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1872-8421</field>
        <field name="keyword">Supraoptic nucleus</field>
        <field name="keyword">Oxidative stress</field>
        <field name="keyword">Nitric oxide synthase</field>
        <field name="keyword">Interleukin-1 beta</field>
        <field name="keyword">Hypoxia-induced factor-1 alpha</field>
        <field name="keyword">Apoptosis</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">NITRIC-OXIDE SYNTHASE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">REAL-TIME PCR</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SEPTIC SHOCK</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">VASOPRESSIN</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PRECURSOR</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">POLYMICROBIAL SEPSIS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GENE-EXPRESSION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PARAVENTRICULAR</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">NUCLEUS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SYSTEMIC INFLAMMATION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">STABLE PEPTIDE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">BRAIN</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Immunology; Neurosciences \&amp; Neurology</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Immunology; Neurosciences</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">44</field>
        <field name="times-cited">7</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">J. Neuroimmunol.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331339700002</field>
        <field name="title">When is a P-space weakly discretely generated</field>
        <field name="Author">Ofelia T. Alas</field>
        <field name="Author">Lucia R. Junqueira</field>
        <field name="Author">Richard G. Wilson</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE BV | TOPOLOGY AND ITS APPLICATIONS | 163</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">A space X is discretely generated at a point x is an element of X if for
            any A subset of X with x is an element of cl(A), there exists a discrete
            set D subset of A such that x is an element of cl(D). The space X is
            discretely generated if it is discretely generated at every point x is
            an element of X. We say that X is weakly discretely generated if for any
            non-closed set A subset of X, there exists a discrete set D subset of A
            such that cl(D)\textbackslash { } A not equal empty set. We obtain new
            results concerning these properties in the class of P-spaces. (C) 2013
            Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">NETHERLANDS</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.topol.2013.10.001</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0166-8641</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1879-3207</field>
        <field name="keyword">Discretely generated space</field>
        <field name="keyword">Weakly discretely generated space</field>
        <field name="keyword">P-space</field>
        <field name="keyword">Lindelof space</field>
        <field name="keyword">Countable extent</field>
        <field name="keyword">Frechet net character</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PRODUCTS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SETS</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Mathematics</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Mathematics, Applied; Mathematics</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">15</field>
        <field name="times-cited">0</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Topology Appl.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000331654200001</field>
        <field name="title">Dimensional reduction of the massless limit of the linearized `New
            Massive Gravity'
        </field>
        <field name="Author">H. A. Biazotti</field>
        <field name="Author">D. Dalmazi</field>
        <field name="Author">G. B. de Gracia</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">SPRINGER | EUROPEAN PHYSICAL JOURNAL C | 74</field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">The so-called `New Massive Gravity' in consists of the Einstein-Hilbert
            action (with minus sign) plus a quadratic term in the curvature (-term).
            Here we perform the Kaluza-Klein dimensional reduction of the linearized
            -term to . We end up with fourth-order massive electrodynamics in ,
            described by a rank-2 tensor. Remarkably, there appears a local symmetry
            in , which persists even after gauging away the Stueckelberg fields of
            the dimensional reduction. It plays the role of a gauge symmetry.
            Although of higher order in the derivatives, the new 2D massive
            electrodynamics is ghost free, as we show here. It is shown, via a
            master action, to be dual to the Maxwell-Proca theory with a scalar
            Stueckelberg field.
        </field>
        <field name="address">USA</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1140/epjc/s10052-014-2747-0</field>
        <field name="ISSN">1434-6044</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1434-6052</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SPIN</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Physics</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Physics, Particles \&amp; Fields</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">15</field>
        <field name="times-cited">0</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Eur. Phys. J. C</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000330913000011</field>
        <field name="title">Enhanced photoabsorption properties of composites of Ti/TiO2 nanotubes
            decorated by Sb2S3 and improvement of degradation of hair dye
        </field>
        <field name="Author">Guilherme Garcia Bessegato</field>
        <field name="Author">Juliano Carvalho Cardoso</field>
        <field name="Author">Bianca Ferreira da Silva</field>
        <field name="Author">Maria Valnice Boldrin Zanoni</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ELSEVIER SCIENCE SA | JOURNAL OF PHOTOCHEMISTRY AND PHOTOBIOLOGY
            A-CHEMISTRY | 276
        </field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">The present work illustrates the great potentiality of Ti/TiO2/Sb2S3
            composite electrode prepared by electrochemical anodization of Ti foil
            in aqueous electrolyte (1 mol L-1 NaH2PO4 + 0.3 wt.\% HF followed by
            chemical bath deposition of Sb2S3) in environmental electrochemistry.
            The electrodes are characterized by deposits of particles of 500 nm of
            diameter formed on the top of TiO2 nanotubes of 900 nm of length, 110 nm
            of diameter and 13 nm of wall thickness. The band gap obtained for
            Ti/TiO2/Sb2S3 composite electrode was 1.68 eV, contributing to strong
            photoabsorption properties of the material in the visible light region
            (lambda &lt;740 nm). The photocurrent on this material is remarkably
            improved in relation to that obtained on comparable nanotubes TiO2
            films. The electrodes promote complete degradation of the investigated
            hair dyeing commercialized as ArianorTyrian Purple (R) after 120 min of
            photoelectrocatalytic oxidation under potential of 1.2V and commercial
            light irradiating under UV/Visible light. Finally, the degradation
            products generated by photoelectrocatalysis were analyzed by HPLC-MS/MS.
            (C) 2013 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">SWITZERLAND</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.jphotochem.2013.12.001</field>
        <field name="ISSN">1010-6030</field>
        <field name="keyword">Bandgap engineering</field>
        <field name="keyword">TiO2 nanotube arrays</field>
        <field name="keyword">TiO2 modification</field>
        <field name="keyword">Photoelectrochemical degradation</field>
        <field name="keyword">Photoelectrochemistry</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SEMICONDUCTOR THIN-FILMS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">TIO2 NANOTUBE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PHOTOELECTROCATALYTIC</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DEGRADATION</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PHOTOCATALYTIC ACTIVITY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">OPTICAL-PROPERTIES</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ORGANIC</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">POLLUTANT</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SOLAR-CELLS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ARRAYS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">ELECTRODES</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">DEPOSITION</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Chemistry</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Chemistry, Physical</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">47</field>
        <field name="times-cited">14</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">J. Photochem. Photobiol. A-Chem.</field>
    </doc>
    <doc>
        <field name="unique-id">ISI:000330153100016</field>
        <field name="title">Lower bounds on the modified K-energy and complex deformations</field>
        <field name="Author">Andrew Clarke</field>
        <field name="Author">Carl Tipler</field>
        <field name="publisher_journal_volume">ACADEMIC PRESS INC ELSEVIER SCIENCE | ADVANCES IN MATHEMATICS | 252
        </field>
        <field name="Year-Month">2010-2019|2014|FEB</field>
        <field name="abstract">Let (X, L) be a polarized Kahler manifold that admits an extremal metric
            in c(1) (L). We show that on a nearby polarized deformation (X', L')
            that preserves the symmetry induced by the extremal vector field of (X,
            L), the modified K-energy is bounded from below. This generalizes a
            result of Chen, Szekelyhidi and Tosatti { [ } 8,35,38] to external metrics.
            Our proof also extends a convexity inequality on the space of Kahler
            potentials due to X.X. Chen { [ } 7] to the extremal metric setup. As an
            application, we compute explicit polarized 4-points blow-ups of CP1 x
            CP1 that carry no extremal metric but with modified K-energy bounded
            from below. (C) 2013 Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved.
        </field>
        <field name="address">USA</field>
        <field name="type">Article</field>
        <field name="language">English</field>
        <field name="DOI">10.1016/j.aim.2013.11.003</field>
        <field name="ISSN">0001-8708</field>
        <field name="EISSN">1090-2082</field>
        <field name="keyword">Modified K-energy</field>
        <field name="keyword">Extremal metrics</field>
        <field name="keyword">Test configuration</field>
        <field name="keyword">Complex</field>
        <field name="keyword">deformation</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">EXTREMAL KAHLER-METRICS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SCALAR CURVATURE</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">PROJECTIVE EMBEDDINGS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">STABILITY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">MANIFOLDS</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">GEOMETRY</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">BUNDLES</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">THEOREM</field>
        <field name="keyword-plus">SPACE</field>
        <field name="research-areas">Mathematics</field>
        <field name="web-of-science-categories">Mathematics</field>
        <field name="number-of-cited-references">40</field>
        <field name="times-cited">0</field>
        <field name="journal-iso">Adv. Math.</field>
    </doc>
</add>